Welcome to the Festival Battle!
Care for a fortune telling?
How about a fortune telling?
Hey, put more enthusiasm into it!
Who's fault do you think it is that we're even
doing this? Asuka was really pissed you know.
What are you talking about? It's all your fault!
Uh, no... You're the one that started
the contests in the first place.
I challenge you to see who's yakisoba is better!
You better start thinking of an excuse
for why you lost!
Black Pig Yakisoba
I turn those words straight back to you!
Springy Fresh Noodles
Why would they want to compete in something like that?
I'm so excited!
Don't be.
Then I'm thrilled?
Don't be that either.
Next is the haunted house contest.
You look terrified!
No I'm not! This is all made up.
Oh, yeah?
Hold on!
Sorry! Unlike you, I have long legs.
Or... are you using the ribbon to
trick us about how long your legs are?
How could I trick you with that?
I just happen to like ribbons, that's all.
That's cold!
Kaori said you look cuter without the ribbon.
No way! Seriously!
Fooled ya!
Ugh you're getting on my nerves, get back here!
The konjac...
Fortune Teller
The Mother of Kitauji
Tarot
Astrology
Blood Type
Next we'll see who has a better fortune.
Senpai, please tell us who has better looking fate.
Okay, leave it to the mother of Kitauji.
First, date of birth?
Of course my fate is going to be better than yours.
I just saw Kaori earlier, she was such an angel.
That was just a coincidence.
No, Kaori and I are bound by the red string of fate.
Don't worry, Senpai doesn't even believe 1% of that crap.
Okay, I understand, date of birth?!
What do you know about senpai?
I ask the same to you, what do you know?
I know everything..!
Like yesterday's side dish, or the pattern on her pajamas.
Seriously?
Don't pull that on me.
Hello? I've been asking for your date of birth!
Bad girls who don't listen will receive divine punishment!
It really is your fault!
How is it my fault?
Looks like we're going to have see
who's fault it really is with a contest!
You're on.
What's going on here?
I'm chewing?
End