Welcome to Maid Outfit!
It's almost time for the Cultural Festival
I'm the perfect maid, if I do say so myself!
Where?! Your costume is way too baggy.
You thought you could wear that?
Big things are good things, so it's fine!
That was in the 60's!
This generation lives with more modesty.
As they say, it's better too big than too small.
No, I don't think that applies to this.
And then maybe, I could get a nice body
and become more grown up looking, like Reina.
When that happens, this maid outfit will fit me perfectly!
Midori with a nice body...
Isn't it too late for that?
Kumiko, I haven't given up on getting a nice body.
If I don't give up, then my wish can be granted!
It'll be a dream come true!
Excuse me! Can you make one Midori size, please!
Okay!
Wait, so you're still going to a resized one?!
Reina...
Sorry for barging in while you're preparing...
It's alright!
What's up? Isn't your class preparing too?
I came when I heard Kumiko was going to put on a maid outfit.
Um, you don't have to come see that...
Reina... please... put this... maid outfit on!!!
Where did you get that from?
From my secret pocket!
You really just borrowed it didn't you?
I know for a fact it'll look good on you.
It's my one and only wish.
You wasted your only wish on a maid outfit?!
You still have your whole life ahead of you..!
What are you two saying?!
If I don't use it now, then when will I use it?
When..?
When you're struggling on a test?
Use it on something more important, Hazuki.
Well... I'm actually terrible at math so...
So there you have it Reina,
will you please put on this maid outfit?
What do you mean?
That's too much.
Me..?
...Is that a no?
Alright.
Thank you!
Kousaka really is easy.
Yep.
It's embarrassing if you stare too much.
Wonderful! Nice boobs, Reina!
Can't you compliment something else?
We're back to boobs again.
Listen here, Kumiko.
A girl's boobs may be small, but that's
no reason for them to mope about it.
I know what I'm saying because mine are small.
Even if they're small, it's fine to think "look at my boobs!"
What the heck...
End