Welcome to the Fireworks Festival Kiss!
Riko...
It's too embarrassing to do that here...
I'm telling you, there's nothing to be embarrassed about.
B-But...
Now then...
Sorry, it's just... not happening!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Riko! Can't you just put up with it?
There was only 3mm left!
No way! I'm too embarrassed!
How did this end up being kissing practice in the first place?
Because!
It's a Summer!
Festival!
And when the fireworks explode...
Smoooooooch~
Why did you two get perfectly in sync just now?
I just felt like the both of you are so
shy that I'd cheer you on a bit.
Cheering? Aren't you just being nosy?
Huh? Weren't you the one that started it in the first place?
I was genuinely cheering them on, that's it.
Come on you two...
Well the fireworks are over, so I'll be on my way...
Riko...
Where are you going?
You better not be thinking about running away.
Are you sure? At this rate you kissing
Gotou will remain in your dreams.
She's right. Summer is all about smooch!
Festivales are all about smooch!
Let's smooch!
You two sure are good friends.
There's no way I would be
friends with that girl.
Just thinking about it gives me goosebumps.
What the?! This bitch.
I'm the one with goosebumps!
Let go of me you two!
Not happening, it's now or never.
You have to prepare yourself.
A girl's gotta have guts!
I think you mean, charm!
I said it before but... kissing Gotou...
It's too embarrassing.  So let's just go home, 'kay?
So where's the protagonist, Gotou?
Listen to me!
We had him go get us drinks while we strategized...
He's so slow... how far did he go just for drinks?
Are you serious?!
What is it?
What a jerk.
Gotou!
It's Gotou's sister.
What's going on?
END