Welcome to the Flying Taki!
Hazuki! Hazuki!
Yeah?
The director said we could each arrange our own
costumes for the concert at the station, right?
Yes.
Seira High School is coming too, we cannot lose
to other schools, even our costumes need to be better.
Really?
That's right!
We must leave a huge impact so that
Kitauji can be remembered!
For example...
What a star! That will definitely look
great on you, I just know it!
It's too heavy!
I wouldn't be able to blow if I wore that!
You have a point... I overlooked that small detail.
Then how about...
Simple is the best!
Just what costume competition is this?!
It's a bit plain isn't it?
Which brings us back to our earlier problem.
Well... if black is no good, then green!
Sapphire!
It's Midori.
No, that was way too lame!
Hazuki, you keep finding problems with this and that.
Obviously! It shouldn't even be us in the first place,
it should be someone that stands out more-
A person that stands out more?
In that case...
Flying Mr. Taki!
That's too much for Mr. Taki!
We'll be unsurpassable if we do this.
It will be an original performance.
Uhh no, there's a whole bunch of permission we'd need.
You're right. Mr. Taki is already 34 years old...
it's probably too flashy for him.
That's not the issue...
Costumes are hard.
Let's just be ourselves.
It's important to not overdo it.
Hazuki...
I have a great costume!
Concert Day
If you climb the stairs we can take a break, Hazuki.
Just a little bit further.
I'll do my best.
That's the last one!
You made it!
I can't anymore...
You did your best,
I am so proud of you, Hazuki.
Midori...
Hazuki...
What's going on here..?
End