Welcome to the Pool!
Sorry for the wait.
It's fine but... where did you go?
Well... I was lost...
Lost? Weren't you boasting earlier
about how this was your "garden"?
Uhm... I didn't say that.
Is something wrong, Midori?
You haven't been speaking this whole time.
No, nothing at all!
I was just admiring what great boobs-
No! I mean... your bikini is so cute that
I couldn't help but stare...
You just said boobs!
Thank you, I think your bathing suit is cute too.
Really? Thanks!
It's so unexpected, since us four usually
talk just about band related things.
Very well said!
I want to talk with Kousaka a tit...
ah... a bit!  I want to become closer friends.
It really is about the boobs!
She just leaked what her true interest was.
It's not like I want to get closer to Kousaka
because of the size of her boobs!
I just feel that we would have a
similar taste in music!
It's good that you have such a proper excuse.
I misunderstood you!
It's just nice to meet cute girls...
I'm not some boob obsessed freak... unlike Kumiko.
I don't like them either!
Wasn't it about music taste?
She was so cute and stylish during
her amazing performance...
and her boobs were so great... that's why
I really want to become your friend, Kosaka.
So it's the boobs!
Yes. Her boobs were so wonderful,
and they looked like a fermata note.
Fermata...
Fermata
I guess they do look alike...
I see.
Oh... that.
Do you understand my fascination with boobs now?
I don't understand it at all!
So please, let's be good friends, Reina!
If you think I'd be good then...
Don't play along...
She's actually playing along?
Thank you so much!
Right, now that I've become good friends with Reina...
Let's go swimming!
We can finally stop talking about boobs.
Let's forget about boobies and go all out swimming!
Perfect boobs...
Booby-senpai!
Where are you going?
In the end it's still about the boobs!?
What's going on..?
End